<facts>
	<fact>
		<header>Did You Know?</header>
		<body>The U. S. imports more than 10 million barrels of oil a day, just over half of our petroleum used is imported</body>
	</fact>
	<fact>
		<header>60% of All Energy</header>
		<body> Light-duty vehicles use more than 60% of all energy used for transportation in the U.S.</body>
	</fact>
	<fact>
		<header>$45 Billion Potential Loss</header>
		<body>In 2009, the U.S. had a loss of $45 Billion in potential GDP as a result of our foreign oil dependence.</body>
	</fact>
	<fact>
		<header>Did You Know?</header>
		<body>The U.S. is the top petroleum importing country in the world, compared to total exports; The top 5 countries we import oil from are: Canada, Saudi Arabia, Mexico, Venezuela, Nigeria and Iraq</body>
	</fact>
	<fact>
		<header>380 Million Gallons of Gas</header>
		<body>Americans use almost 380 million gallons of gasoline a day, approximately 1.2 gallons per person.</body>
	</fact>
	<fact>
		<header>Production Can't Keep Up</header>
		<body>By the year 2035, petroleum consumption for transportation is expected to grow to more than 17 million barrels per day; at that time, with current production levels, the gap between U.S. production and transportation consumption will be about 5 million barrels per day.</body>
	</fact>
	<fact>
		<header>Did You Know?</header>
		<body>Each 5 miles you drive over 60 MPH, is like paying almost another quarter per gallon for gas.</body>
	</fact>
	<fact>
		<header>Idly Wasting Money</header>
		<body>Idling wastes 6 billion gallons of fuel annually; many states have passed laws to make idling illegal FYI (CA is one, they have gone so far as to ban drive through service on new construction, IE: banks, fast food locations, drug stores, etc.)</body>
	</fact>
	<fact>
		<header>Improve Your Gas Mileage</header>
		<body>Maintaining the speed limit and reducing aggressive driving could potentially improve your fuel economy by 1/3.</body>
	</fact>
	<fact>
		<header>Helping Reduce Petroleum Use</header>
		<body> Since 1993, Clean Cities has reduced 3B gallons of petroleum and aided in the deployment of more than 1/2 a million alternative fuel vehicles</body>
	</fact>
</facts>


